Guide to the Amos Vogel Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Films, 1896-2001
  - Subseries II.1: Film Files, 1896-1993
    - Margaret Mead: Reflections, undated (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Marguerite, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Marie et le Curé, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Marilyn Times Five, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Les Marines, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Marjoe, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Marketa Lazarvoná, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Gregory Markopoulos Films, 1965-1967 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - A Married Couple, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - The Married Woman, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - La Marseillaise, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Martyrs of Love, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Massacre For an Orgy, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Massnahmen gegen Fanatiker, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Masters of the Sky, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Masturbation Men, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Mau Mau, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - The Maze, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - The Maze, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Mbira Dza Vadzimu: Religion at Family Level, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Mean Streets, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - The Mechanics of Love, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Medea, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Meditation on the End of Human Life, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Meditation on Violence, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Medium Cool, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Melies Films Seen in Oberhausen, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - George Melies File, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Melies: Five Fantastic Films, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Memorandum, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Memories of Underdevelopment, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Memory of the Camps, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Memory of Justice, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Men Over the Clouds, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Ménilmontant, 1925 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Men's Lives, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Merc, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Merchant of Four Seasons, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Merry Go Round, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - The Merry Widow, 1925 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Meshes in the Afternoon, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Message From Mississippi, undated (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Messidor, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Metanoia, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Metanomen, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Mexico: The Frozen Revolution, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Mickey Mouse in Vietnam, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Mickey One, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Middle of the World, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Midvinterblot, 1950s (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - The Milky Way, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - The Henry Miller Odyssey, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Millhouse, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Le Million, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Minnie and Moskowitz, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - A Miracle, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Miracle in Milan, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - The Mirage, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Mirror, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - The Mischief Makers, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Mr. Freedom, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Mr. Frenhofer and the Minotaur, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Misto, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Mississippi Mermaid, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Misunderstanding, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Mizoguchi: Life of a Film Director, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Modern Times, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Monkey Into Man, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Monsieur Jean Claude Vaucherin, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Monsieur Tête, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Montenegro, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Moon, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Moonbird, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Moonwalk One, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Moratorium, undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - More, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - More Nuclear Power Stations, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Mosaic in Confidence, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Moscow Does Not Believe in Tears, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Mosori Monika, undated (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - The Most, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - The Most Beautiful Age, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - The Most Important Wish, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Mother, 1926 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - The Mother and the Whore, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Mother Joan of the Angels, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Mother's Day, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - A Mother's Heart, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Motif, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Motion Perception I and II, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Motion Picture, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Mouchette, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Mounting Tension, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Mouth Agape, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - A Movie, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Edvard Munch, undated (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - The Murder of Fred Hampton, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Muriel, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Murmur of the Heart, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Museum at Auschwitz, undated (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - La Musica, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - The Music Box, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - The Music Room, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Music Studio: Harry Partch, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - My Apprenticeship, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - My Girlfriend's Wedding, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - My House, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - My House, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - My Name Is Oona, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - My Night With Maud, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - My Sister, My Love, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Le Mystere Koumiko, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Mysteries of the Organism, 1971, (2 Folders) (Box 35, Folder 7 to 8)
    - The Myth of Naro, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - My Universities, 1940 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Nadir, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - N!AI: Story of a Kung Woman, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Nasissant, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Naked Prey, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Nana, Mom and Me, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Napoleon, 1927 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Narcissus, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - NASA Footage: Earth From Space, undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Der Nationaltag, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Native Land, 1942 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Natural Habitat, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Naughty Nurse, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - The Navigator, 1924 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Nazarin, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Nazarth-- Poster (Box 15-K-5)
    - Nazi Features, 1933-1944 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Nazi Propaganda Films I, 1934-1946 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Nazi Propaganda Films II, 1933-1937, 1971-1980 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Necrology, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Neighbors, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Nemec's Film on Student Demonstrators, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Pablo Neruda, Poet, undated (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Neuron, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - New Art/New Artists, 1980s (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - The New Earth, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Le Nez, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Nice Time, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Night and Fog, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - A Night at the Opera, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Nights of Cabiria, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - 1941, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - 1900, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - 9 Variations on a Dance Theme, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Nobody Has the Last Laugh, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - No Credit, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - No Lies, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - No Man's Land, 1931 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - No More Fleeing, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Norien Ten, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Northern Lights, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - A Nose, undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Nosferatu, The Vampyre, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - N ostalgia, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - N:O:T:H:I:N:G, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Nothing But a Man, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Nothing Happened This Morning, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - La Notte, 1961, 1980-1983 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Now, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Now That the Buffalo's Gone, undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - N.U., 1949 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Nuba, undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Nuptiae, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - N.Y., N.Y., 1958 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Object Lesson, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Odd Obsession, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - O Cangaceiro, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Occurrence at Owl Creek, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - O Dreamland, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Oedipus, 1950s (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Offon, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Of the Dead, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Oh Dem Watermelons, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Oh! What a Lovely War!, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Los Ojos, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - L'Oiseau de la Sagesse, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - O.K., 1964 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Old, Borrowed and Stag, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Los Olvidados, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Olympia, 1936 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - On a Most Beautiful Meadow, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Onan, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Once Upon A Time, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - One Man's Laundry, undated (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - One A.M., 1968 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Onibaba, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - On the Edge, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - On the Edge, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - On the Marriage Broker…, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - L'Opéra Mouffe, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Operation Abolition, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Operation Correction, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Operation Teutonic Sword, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - OP Hop/Hop Op, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Orange, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Ordet, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Ordinary Courage, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Orpheus, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Os Fuzis, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - O Tannenbaum, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Othon, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Otmar Baur Presents…, undated (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Our Africa Trip, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Our Hospitality, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Our Lady of the Spheres, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Our Lady of the Turks, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Out One/Spectre, 1972-1974 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Overture, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Pacific 231, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - A Page of Madness, 1926 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Paint, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Paisan, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Palestine, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - La Paloma, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Pandora's Box, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Panola, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Paper Negatives, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Paradise Now, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Paris Belongs to Us, 1958-1960 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Particularly Valuable, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Pasadena Freeway Stills, 1974-1976, (2 Folders) (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Pas de Deux, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Passenger, 1961-1963 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Passion of Anna, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - The Passion of Joan of Arc, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - The Path, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - The Path, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Pather Panchali, 1952-1955 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Pat's Birthday, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Pattern For a Sunday Afternoon, undated (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Paul Delveaux ou Les Femmes Defenoues, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Paul Jacobs and the Nuclear Gang, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Paul Tomkowicz: Street Railway Switchman, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Peace Mandala, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Peasants of the Second Fortress, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - The Pedestrian, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Peege, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Peep Show, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Pen Point Percussion, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - People and Their Guns, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - People Meet and Sweet Music Fills the Heart, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - People on Sunday, 1929 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Performance 520, undated (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Persona, 1965-1971 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Pestilent City, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Le Petit Soldat, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Le Petit Theatre de Jean Renoir, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - The Petrified Dog, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Phans of Jersey City, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - The Phantom of Liberty, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - The Photographer, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Pianissimo, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Pickpocket, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Pierrot le Fou, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Pigpen, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Piknik mit Weissman, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Pilgrimage, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Pilots in Pajamas, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Pink Flamingoes, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Pitfall (Kashi To Kodomo), 1962 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Le Plaisir, 1951 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Plato in America, undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Playtime, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - The Pleasure Garden, 1925 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Poem 8, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Polanski Meets Macbeth, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Jackson Pollack, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Porch Glider, undated (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Porklips Now, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Pornographic Films, undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Portrait, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Portrait of Jason, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Possibly a Special on the Bag, undated (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Possum Living, undated (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Potemkin, 1925 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Postschi, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Potlatch, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - The Potted Psalm, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Power, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Power of Plants, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Powers of Ten, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Pow Wow, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Praise Marx and Pass the Ammunition, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Prato Palomares, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Pravda, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - A Prepared Text, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - President’s One Minute Movies: Moisture, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Price of Peace, 1980s (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Princess Yang Kwei Fei, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Print Generation, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Private Parts, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Privilege, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Professor Mamlock, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - The Projectionist, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Promised Land, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Promised Lands, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Prune Flat, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Psyche, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Psycho, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Psycho Montage, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Puce Moment, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Punishment Park, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Punking Out, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Pull My Daisy, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - The Puritan, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Putney Swope, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Putting the Babies Back, undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - The Queen, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Queen Kelly, 1928 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Que Hazar, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - The Rain People, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Rape, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Rashomon, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - The Rats Awakening, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Raven’s End, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Ray Gun Virus, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Razor Blades, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - The Reality of Karel Appel, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - La Reconstitution, undated (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Recreation One, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Recreation Two, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Recruits in Ingolstadt, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - The Red and the White, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Red Beard, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Red Desert, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Red Psalm, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Red Squad, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Reed: Mexico Insurgente, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Reefer Madness, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 44)
    - Reflections on Black, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 45)
    - ReflexFilm/FamilyFilm, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - La Region Centrale, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Related by Choice, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Relativity, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - La Religieuse, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Remedial Reading Comprehension, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Renaissance, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Report, 1963-1967 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Report, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Report on the Party and the Guests, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Repulsion, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Requiem for 500,000, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Le Retour, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Le Retour D’Un Adventurier, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Return of the Lost Son, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - The Return of the Secaucus, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - The Revealer, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - The Revolutionary Was a Cop, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Revolution Until Victory, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Rhinozeros, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Rhythmus 21, 1921 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Rich and Judy, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Ricky and Rocky, undated (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Leni Riefenstahl: Bibliography, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Rien Que Les Heures, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Risen Indeed, undated (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Rise of Louis XIV, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - The Rite, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - The Rite, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - The Rite of Love and Death, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Ritual in Transfigured Time, 1945-1946 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Riverun, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Larry Rivers, undated (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Roads of Exile, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Ro Go Pag, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Role of My Family in the World Revolution, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Roma, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - La Ronde, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - The Room, undated (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - The Room, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - The Rose-Covered Cottage, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - La Rose et Le Réséda, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    - Rotate the Body, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 43)
    - Andrei Roublev, 1962-1967 (Box 41, Folder 44)
    - The Round-Up, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 45)
    - Rubin On Schools, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - Ruby, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Rules of the Game, 1938 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - The Running, Jumping and Standing Still Film, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Running Shadow, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Runs Good, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - St. Matthew’s Passion, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Saint Michael Has a Rooster, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - La Salamandre, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Salesman, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Salo, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Sally’s Hounds, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Salvatore Guliano, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Samadhi, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Le Samourai, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Sandra, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Le Sang, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Saturday Morning, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Fellini Satyricon, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Sangus Series, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Sausalito, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - The Savage Messiah, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - The Scandalous Adventures of Buraikan, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Schmeerguntz, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Schoolgirl, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Joseph Schultz, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Schwechater, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Science Fiction, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Science Friction, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Scorpio Rising, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Screening Room, undated (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Screen Test, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Sean, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Searching Eye, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - The Sea Shell and the Clergyman, 1928 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - The Second Circle, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - The Secret Cinema, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - The Secrete of Life, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Secrets of a Soul, 1925 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - El Secuestrador, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Seduction of Mimi, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - See-Saw Seams, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - George Segal, undated (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - See You at Mao, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - Seifriz on Protoplasm, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Selbstschuesse, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - The Selling of the Pentagon, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Senso, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Seven Beauties, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - The Seven Bridges of Koenigsberg, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Seven Chances, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - The Seven Samurai, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - The Seventeenth Parallel, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - The Seventh Seal, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - 79 Springtimes, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Sex (Israel), 1971 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Sexual Freedom in Denmark, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - The Sexually Mature Adult, undated (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Shadows, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Shadow of an Apple, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Shadows of Forgotten Ancestors, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Shame, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Shakespeare Wallah, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Shameless Old Lady, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - She and He, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - She Done Him Wrong, 1933 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Sheltering Sky, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Sherlock Jr., 1924 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - The Shining, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Shipyard, 1934-1935 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Shoah, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Shoot the Moon, undated (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Shoot the Piano Player, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Shop on High Street, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Shoulder Arms, 1918 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Sighet, Sighet, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Sigmund Freud’s Dora, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Signs of Life, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - The Silence, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Silent Scream, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - The Silent Witness, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Silver City, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - Michel Simon, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - Simon, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - Simon of Desert, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 41)
    - Un Simple Histoire, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - Isaac Singer’s Nightmare & Mrs. Pupko’s Beard, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - The Sin of Jesus, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Sirius Remembered, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Six Filmmakers in Search of a Wedding, undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Six in Paris, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - The Sixties, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - 69, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - 69-- Poster (Box 15-K-5)
    - Skater Dater, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Skullduggery, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Sky Capers, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Sky Is Gray, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Skypiece, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Sleep, 1963-1964 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Sleeper, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - The Sluice, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - The Smiling Madame Beudet, 1922 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Smoke, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Snapshots, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Socrates, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Sodoma, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Solaris, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Soleil O, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Soliloquy, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Soliloquy, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Soma Touch, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Song of the Godbody, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 26)